<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>peeriX | Open Source Solutions for Business on PeeriX</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in peeriX | Open Source Solutions for Business on PeeriX</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Atanas (Jack) Argirov</title>
      <link>/team/argirov/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Nov 2018 10:47:58 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/argirov/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Development</title>
      <link>/services/software-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/software-development/</guid>
      <description>Web or client/server based software Web based Applications Database Applications Network Services System Services Payment Systems Biometric Systems Re-engineering Automation Glue Code Selenium web testing automation </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Source Software (OSS)</title>
      <link>/services/oss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/oss/</guid>
      <description>Open Source Software (OSS) We provide OSS software consulting, deployment, tuning and support services for wide range of software as:
PostgreSQL Selecting target infrastructure Performance tuning High Availability Clustering and replication Migrations Backup Monitoring Ongoing support Unix Distributions Debian, Ubuntu, RedHat, CentOS, SuSE, FreeBSD, OpenBSD
Web Servers nginx, Apache
Load Balancers HAProxy
Mail Postfix, Dovecot, Sendmail, Cyrus
Server Backends Django, Flask, Tomcat
Version Control Systems and Continuous Integration (CI) git, Mercurial, Jenkins, GitLab</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>/services/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/training/</guid>
      <description>Training
C Programming Python Programming Java Programming Linux FreeBSD SQL Databases Web Application Development with Javascript + frameworks (Vue.js / React.js) Systems Management Version Control Systems Effective Testing Development toolchains - Python, Java Continuous Integration (CI) pipelines </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosted Services</title>
      <link>/services/hosted-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:34 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/hosted-services/</guid>
      <description>We take care of your applications hosting it on purposefully built resilient infrastructure.
Custom Services Mail Servers Web Applications Monitoring </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>/services/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Consulting
Product Evaluation Specification Security OSS Support IT Organization Project Management Network Management and Best practices LIR services as member of RIPE </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remote Support</title>
      <link>/services/remote-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:54 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/remote-support/</guid>
      <description>We can remotely fix problems on your Windows workstation/server, Apple PC or UNIX machines.
For Windows or Apple&amp;rsquo;s Mac OS based PC please download: TeamViewer
Once installed successfully, please call us on +44 (0) 203 3932023 to provide us with a temporary access to your PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Systems Management</title>
      <link>/services/system-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/system-management/</guid>
      <description>Unix infrastructure Setup and Operations Network infrastructure Thin clients based on diskless Linux terminals Windows infrastructure Virtualized enviroments Containerized Applications based on Docker or FreeBSD&amp;rsquo;s Jails Full automation of required provisioning, configuration management and application deployment with Ansible Storage servers based on ZFS or Ceph Automated backup solutions on-site or off-site with built-in encryption Security hardening and evaluation services Monitoring Mail Servers (with optional spam filters) Custom Software Packaging for mass deployment/distribution </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>e: hello@peerix.net </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>PeeriX (Peer Exchange) is a group of technology veterans with professional experience spanning few decades. We have been programming since the era of IBM 360s and DEC&amp;rsquo;s VAXStations, Apple II, early days PCs on 808x, DEC Alphas to modern day CPU architectures.
We have been developing software on all major operating systems (OS), but our core expertise is UNIX based systems.
From high-frequency trading systems to biometric authentication and payments systems, we have deep and wide knowledge of what is involved in building performant, reliable and secure software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
